Search for:  

Toggle navigation

Search for:  

Privacy Policy
==============

Updated on 01/08/2023

[Wisemetering](https://www.wisemetering.com/ "Go to Wisemetering.") > Privacy Policy

LMSI – Engineering, SA (hereinafter Society) will always process the personal data of the users of its Website in accordance with the Privacy Policy described on this page, in a lawful and equitable manner, for specific and legitimate purposes and only to the extent that is necessary for these purposes, in strict compliance with the principles described in this policy, Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Regulation on Data Protection) and applicable data protection legislation, in all personal data processing activities.

LMSI’s Privacy Policy is framed in the normative body of protection of its personal data and is complemented by the other documents of this normative body, which includes rules and procedures for the management of security and privacy of personal data.

#### **a. Controller identification and contacts**

LMSI – Engineering, SA, headquartered at Rua Afonso Annes Penedo, 56, 1950-014 Lisbon, registered at the Commercial Registry Office under the number of Person of Lisbon with the registration number and legal person 515389080, with a share capital of € 1,000,000.00, is – in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation and other legislation on the protection of personal data in force in the countries where it operates – the Controller for the processing of personal data that we collect when registering and browsing this site.

#### **b. What categories of Personal data are processed**

For the purposes of this policy, any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (data subject) is considered **personal data**. The data subject can be identified directly or indirectly, namely through an identification number or through specific characteristics of their physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural, or social identity.

The Company only collects personal data that is necessary for the purpose for which it is intended. If the user intends to provide information about other personal data, he must do so voluntarily, since this data is not requested, nor is it necessary.

The provision of the user’s personal data is not a legal or contractual obligation, however, if you do not provide it, it may make our response unfeasible.

The Society on its website collects and processes data resulting from job applications such as: name, date of birth, tax identification number, identification number, email address, civil mobile phone number, and any other data contained in CVs sent or any others that the candidate intends to provide voluntarily.

#### **c. Data retained for the required period**

The Company will keep the personal data shared only for the period necessary for processing according to the respective purpose.

After the end of this period, the company will either make the data anonymous or safely destroy it.

#### **d. Who personal data is shared with**

In order to better fit an application, we may share the data with other companies in LMSI to which the Company belongs, established in the Member States of the European Union. Transfers of personal data to third countries will only be made with your consent. These companies have the appropriate security measures in place to protect your data.

#### **e. What are your rights and how can you exercise them**

The Company provides the holders of personal data for which it is responsible for processing the processes and tools that allow it to exercise, in a timely manner, the rights that are recognized under the terms of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, namely:

1. Information to the holder of personal data;
2. Access to information about your personal data;

* That we transfer the personal data you provided to us to another entity;

1. Correction of your data or updating;
2. The deletion of your personal data;
3. The cessation of the processing of your personal data when you decide to oppose its treatment;

* Limitation of the processing of your data;
* Transferring your data to another LMSI company;

On the other hand, you can always and at any time withdraw your consent without compromising the lawfulness of the treatment carried out based on the consent previously given.

In order to ensure that personal data is not accessed by employees of the Company without legitimacy for the purposes for which they were collected, the Company established a process for assigning access to information (in physical or logical format) and to personal data based on in the “need to know” principle. This principle dictates that only access that is strictly necessary for the performance of users’ functions should be assigned.

The access profiles to the information systems are configured in order to guarantee that only authorized users can access personal data according to the specificity of each purpose.

To exercise your rights or whenever you have any questions about LMSI’s Privacy Policy and the use of your personal data, you can contact the Company by email to the address: mjoao.donato@lmsi.pt

You can file a complaint with the supervisory authority.

WiseMetering is an energy management platform focused on optimizing consumption and reducing costs. Providing monitoring solutions for buildings and the retail market.

##### The Platform

##### Resources

##### Additional Links

Wisemetering - LM Group. All rights reserved.

### Would you like to become a Wisemetering partner?

Fill out the form to take an active role in the life of this energy management platform!

Ramo  
—Please choose an option—ArquitecturaAuditorias & Energia & SCE & SGCIEBanca & SegurosCâmaras MunicipaisConstruçãoData CentersDesenvolvimento de SoftwareDesportoDistribuidores de Equipamentos,EducaçãoEmpreiteirosEntretenimentoFacility ServicesFarmacêuticaFísica e AmbienteFundos ImobiliáriosGestão de EdifíciosGestão de ObrasIndústriaMediaMuseusParques de EstacionamentoParticularProjectistas / EngenhariaProjectoPromotores ImobiliáriosPúblicoReal Estate & CondomíniosRestauraçãoRetail

Ao enviar este formulários eu concordo com os [Termos de Uso](https://www.wisemetering.com/termos-e-condicoes/) e [Políticas de Privacidade.](https://www.wisemetering.com/politica-de-privacidade/)

×

We use cookies on our website to provide a relevant experience, remembering your favorites and future visits. By clicking "Accept", you agree to the use of ALL cookies.

SettingsACCEPT

Cookie Settings

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessários

 Necessários

Always Enabled

Os cookies necessários são absolutamente essenciais para o funcionamento adequado do site. Esta categoria inclui apenas cookies que garantem funcionalidades básicas e recursos de segurança do site. Esses cookies não armazenam nenhuma informação pessoal.

Não necessários

 Não necessários

Quaisquer cookies que possam não ser particularmente necessários para o funcionamento do site e sejam usados ​​especificamente para coletar dados pessoais do usuário por meio de análises, anúncios e outros conteúdos incorporados são denominados cookies não necessários. É obrigatório obter o consentimento do usuário antes de executar esses cookies no seu site.

SAVE & ACCEPT
